

## **ABOUT ME**

Purpose: Based on my previous work experience, moving forward my goal is to be a successful at full stack development. I am keen to improve my professional knowledge and gain new skills relevant to my role. I'm committed I am open to innovative solutions, and maintain a proactive attitude at all times. My continuous professional development is important to me, consequently I seek opportunities that help me improve both in my career and as a person

#### CONTACT

PHONE:

+36 70 727 9333

EMAIL:

judit.aczel1@protonmail.com

# JUDIT ACZÉL

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Orina Kft. Softwaredeloper

#### 27/08/2021-

-Developed exclusive business applications on a unique platform (Low Code Platform). Mainly high-level use of MS SQL (stored procedure, functions, triggers) in addition to XML programming, HTML/CSS, AngularJS. Daily use of Azure DevOps and Git version tracking. Development of C# interfaces. Use of REST API and Webservices.

## Black Cell Magyarország Kft. SOC L1 Analyst

#### 02/01/2020-04/02/2021

- -Carried out client system monitoring of the company's contracted customers with (IBM Qradar, Splunk, Vectra, MCAS, O365, JIRA, Alien Vault, WAF... and some of the online investigating scanner) reporting and investigating events.
- -Assisted in the development, maintenance and security of the Wordpress websites of my company in Hungarian and English / and an external company.
- -Developed a WordPress Wiki Knowledge Base for internal use.

Web: https://blackcell.hu; https://blackcell.io; https://welovedigital.hu;

## MKK Magyar Követeléskezelő Zrt Application expert

## 06/08/2018-13/12/2019

- -PL/SQL database programming store procedures, triggers
- -Preparation of financial and accounting tasks and statements (PL/SQL és Power BI)
- -Assessment of the development needs of the internal system (Kökény .Net application), documentation and sending development tickets to external developers.
- -SQL and application log analysis from Kökény system
- -We used TOPDESK as a ticket system
- -The second main task was to completely modernize the company's existing website, with online payment integration.

Web: https://mkkzrt.hu

#### KMPG Global Services Hungary SharePoint analyst

## 02/01/2017 - 01/08/2018

- -SharePoint collab site programming, site groups and user's management with permissions settings
- -SharePoint, SharePoint Designer and C # development tasks
- -MS SQL and SSRS report generation
- -ULS Viewer, Event logs, SQL database logs analysis
- -TFS ticket system
- -I was responsible for migrating project. The migration process was from SharePoint 2007 to SharePoint 2013 with collab web site with content and settings.

# **Delta csoport** Application developer

#### 01/06/2016 - 01/12/2016

- -SharePoint servers (2013, 2016), Windows server (2012R2), SQL servers (2012, 2014) installing and configuring, managing user groups permissions.
- -SharePoint Designer, SharePoint Branding Development Competencies and skills
- -Microsoft IIS web server, SCVMM and Hyper-V virtual environments installation and configuration knowledge
- -MS SQL, PowerShell, Caml guery creation,
- -SharePoint and C# development tasks
- -Event viewer, ULS Viewer, log analysis,
- -SharePoint deployments with PowerShell and C #
- -Release preparation and installation on client systems
- -Building an auto build system with Team Foundation Server

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

## Szent György Media and Informatics Secondary School (2016)

Software development OKJ (54-213-05)

## **Training 360 (2017-2018)**

CSharp programming (Microsft 20483)

Administering Windows Server 2012 (Microsoft 20411)

Installing and configuring Windows Server 2012 (Microsoft 20410)

## **HOBBIES AND INTEREST**

#### **Hobbies**

In my free time, I prefer to be active, I like walking and cycling when the weather allows. In the summer, I always go kayaking with my mother to Lake Balaton, and in the winter, I usually go to gym.

## **Interests**

I am very interested in CMS systems, PHP coding, databases, UI / UX solutions, e-commerce websites building. I enjoy working with them and building them. I want to deal more deeply with website development technologies, so I take part in online courses.

# **OTHER EXPERIENCE**

I am self-taught and keen to maintain an up-to-date knowledge about current website development trends at all times. I have the skills to work using PHP frameworks such as CAKE PHP, Laravel and I am competent at JavaScript libraries like JQuery, AJAX, Typescript, AngularJS, ReactJS and JavaScript frameworks like VUE.js and NODE JS. CSS 3 and CSS framework like Bootstrap5. WordPress, Joomla. In addition, I am familiar with GIT, GITHUB and GitBucket. Docker.

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother language: Hungarian

## English

Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	Writing
B2	B2	A2	A2	A2

## German

Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	Writing
B1	B1	A2	A2	A2